Pickleball.
匹克球。
It's got nothing to do with pickles – it's a sport.
它和泡菜毫无关系——它是一项运动。
It has been described as a combination of tennis, badminton and table tennis.
它被描述为网球、羽毛球和乒乓球的结合体。
Picture a small plastic ball soaring through the air that you need to bat back to your partner, or partners.
想象一下，一个小小的塑料球在空中飞舞，你需要把它击打回给你的搭档或搭档们。
Many Brits are listening to their inner athlete and picking up this racket game.
许多英国人听从他们内心运动员的召唤，开始玩起这项执拍运动。
In the UK, there are currently around 7,000 players, according to Pickleball England.
根据英格兰匹克球协会的数据，英国目前约有7,000名球员。
But the association aims to have more than 25,000 players by 2025 and is even attempting to get the sport played as part of promotion for the 2028 Olympics.
但该协会的目标是到2025年拥有超过25,000名球员，甚至正试图让这项运动作为2028年奥运会推广活动的一部分。
How exactly do you play this game?
这项运动到底怎么玩？
Well, it can be played indoors or outdoors and it can be played as a singles or doubles game.
嗯，它可以在室内或室外进行，可以是单打或双打比赛。
There are a few easy-to-understand rules.
有几个很容易理解的规则。
The ball is served underhand and should be batted diagonally across the court.
发球必须下手发球（手不过肩），并且应该斜线击打过网。
On the first two hits, the ball has to bounce, but after that, players are free to volley.
在前两次击球时，球必须落地弹起一次，但之后，球员可以随意截击。
To win a point, the defending side must miss the ball.
要赢得一分，防守方必须没接到球。
So, why is it popular?
那么，它为什么受欢迎呢？
Firstly, it appears to be a game for all ages.
首先，它似乎是一项适合所有年龄段的运动。
The ball is lightweight because it's full of holes.
球很轻，因为上面布满孔洞。
This means that, when batting, there is much less impact on the body than when hitting a tennis ball, for example.
这意味着击球时，对身体的冲击力比打网球之类的球要小得多。
Elaine Brown, who is in her 50s and a regular pickleball player, told news organisation, The Guardian why she loves the sport.
50多岁的伊莱恩·布朗经常打匹克球，她告诉新闻机构《卫报》她为什么热爱这项运动。"
"It's good exercise, it's strategic, it can be as hard or as easy as you want it to be, and most of the time it's just good fun."
这是很好的锻炼，讲究策略，你想让它多难或多容易都可以，而且大多数时候就是很好玩。"
And the social aspect and low-impact nature of the game has been attracting players worldwide, creating a blossoming community of pickleball enthusiasts, such as celebrities Bill Gates and Leonardo DiCaprio.
这项运动的社交性和低冲击性一直在吸引世界各地的玩家，形成了一个蓬勃发展的匹克球爱好者群体，其中包括名人比尔·盖茨和莱昂纳多·迪卡普里奥。
So, if you fancy picking it up, find your local pickleball court and give it a go!
所以，如果你想尝试一下，找到你当地的匹克球场，去试一试吧！